http://www.marineengineparts.com/privacy-policy/

Order by Phone: (631) 722-5700
Engine & Drive PartsStern Drive EngineGas Inboard EngineOutdrives & TransmissionsOutboardsTools & ManualsDiesel Inboard EngineGeneratorsOils & LubesAnodesPaint-Engine & Stern DriveFel-Pro GasketsPropellersNoise ReductionRacor Air & Crankcase FiltersSpark Plugs
Stern Drive Engine
MerCruiser
Volvo Penta
OMC
> Shop All
Gas Inboard Engine
MerCruiser
Volvo Penta
Crusader
> Shop All
Outdrives & Transmissions
MerCruiser R/MR, ’78-’82
MerCruiser Alpha One, ’83-’90
MerCruiser Alpha One, (GEN II)
> Shop All
Outboards
Mercury-Mariner
Yamaha
Evinrude-Johnson
> Shop All
Generators
Onan Generator
> Shop All
Exhaust & CoolingComplete Manifold & Riser KitsExhaust Manifolds & RisersExhaust Mufflers & FittingsWater Pumps & Service KitsHeat ExchangersOil & Transmission CoolersThru Hulls, Valves & FittingsIntake StrainersAir Conditioner PumpsThermostats & HousingsHoseCoolantTools & Maintenance
Complete Manifold & Riser Kits
Exhaust Manifolds & Risers
MerCruiser Exhaust
Crusader Exhaust
Volvo Penta Exhaust
> Shop All
Exhaust Mufflers & Fittings
"Lift" Style
Tools & Maintenance
Controls & SteeringControl BoxesControl CablesHydraulic SteeringMechanical SteeringPower SteeringSteering WheelsSteering AccessoriesTilt Tubes & AccessoriesTools
Control Boxes
Teleflex/SeaStar Binnacle Top Mount
Teleflex/SeaStar Side Mount
Mercury OEM Control Boxes
> Shop All
Control Cables
CC170 OMC 400 Series - Prior to 1979
CC205 OMC 479 Standard Series - 1979 & Newer
Tools
FuelCarburetorsFuel GaugesFuel PumpsFuel InjectionFuel Filters & Water SeparatorsTools-FuelFuel Hose & Fuel LinesFuel AdditivesFuel FittingsFuel Tanks & AccessoriesRacor Fuel Filters & Water Separators
Racor Fuel Filters & Water Separators
Racor Gasoline Filters & Water Separators
Racor Diesel Filters & Water Separators
> Shop All
Fuel Filters & Water Separators
Inboard & Stern Drive Filters
Outboard Fuel Filters
Diesel Engine Fuel Filters
Tools - Fuel
PlumbingPumpsBilgeDomestic Fresh Water SystemWater Heaters & AccessoriesThru Hulls, Strainers, Valves & FittingsMarine Sanitation & ToiletsHose By The Foot Or BulkTanksDeck Fills & VentsEngine FlushingVentilation
Pumps
Air Conditioning Pumps
Baitwell & Livewell Pumps
Bilge Pumps
> Shop All
Bilge
Bilge Pumps & Float Switches
Bilge Pump Hose
> Shop All
ElectricalGauges & InstrumentsMarine Grade Wire & ConnectorsMarinco Shore PowerSmartPlugElectrical SwitchesBatteries & AccessoriesCircuit Breakers & PanelsFuses & Buss BarsLED & Incandescent LightingTrim Tab Kits & AccessoriesChargers, Inverters & IsolatorsBilge Pumps, Floats & BlowersHorns & Wipers
Gauges & Instruments
Faria Gauges
Sierra Gauges
Blue Sea Systems
> Shop All
Marine Grade Wire & Connectors
Battery Cable
Battery Cable Premade
> Shop All
Accessories & MaintenanceDeck & Hull HardwarePaints, Varnishes, Epoxies, Sealants & SuppliesWatersports & FishingAnchor & DockingNavigation & ElectronicsOils, Lubes & GreasesCleaners & WaxesTrailerSafetyTools & Service AidsFasteners
Fasteners
Stainless Steel-SAE
Stainless Steel-Metric
Galvanized
> Shop All
Deck & Hull Hardware
Deck Hardware
Rail Fittings-Stainless Steel-7/8"
Rail Fittings-Stainless Steel-1"
> Shop All
Paints, Varnishes, Epoxies, Sealants & Supplies
Paints
Varnishes & Wood Treatments
Teak Oils & Cleaners
> Shop All
Anchor & Docking
Anchors & Windlasses
Privacy Policy
Thank you for visiting www.MarineEngineParts.com (a division of Lighthouse Marine Supply). Marineengineparts.com & Partman.com are wholly owned subsidiaries of Lighthouse Marine Supply & Lighthouse Marine Distributors
We are committed to protecting the privacy and security of your personal information. marineEngineParts.com does not rent, sell, or exchange information about our customers to any party for any reason. To learn more, please read the privacy policy that follows.
This policy sets out how MarineEngineParts.com uses and protects any information that you give MarineEngineParts.com when you use this website. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using our website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy policy. This policy does not apply to the practices and policies of any companies not affiliated with MarineEngineParts.com to which this site links or that links to this site.
We consider your account information to be private, and we keep this information on a secure server to protect it from outside parties. We use the information only for the limited purposes of processing your orders, administering our site, and notifying you of products or special offers that may be of interest to you (only if you select to be included on out mailing list). We do not share your private information with anyone.
COLLECTING INFORMATION
MarineEngineParts.com collects personally identifiable information from customers only when specifically and knowingly provided by you. Examples of the type of information collected are name, shipping and billing address, phone number, email address, and credit card information. We collect personal information when you register as a member with MarineEngineParts.com, order products from MarineEngineParts.com, visit www.MarineEngineParts.com, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. We use the information collected to better understand your needs, fulfill your specific requests for products and services, improve our products and services, and to contact you regarding any offers that may be off interest.
INFORMATION USE
MarineEngineParts.com does not rent, sell or exchange information about our customers, and all information provided to us remains absolutely confidential, except that:
We may share information to trusted partners who need to access your customer information in order to provide operational or other support services to us. These companies are not authorized to use any information we share with them for any other purpose.
We gather only customer information that is needed to administer business, provide superior service and communicate with you offers on products and services that we believe will be of interest to you.
We may periodically send promotional email about new products, special offers, service announcements, and administrative messages using the email address, which you have provided.
We limit access to your personal information to those employees who need it to carry out their business functions. We educate our employees about our policies and practices in regard to safeguarding customer information; preventing its unauthorized access or disclosure; and, ensuring its proper handling.
We may be required by law to disclose such information in response to subpoenas, court orders, or requests from law-enforcement officials.
CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures that comply with federal regulations to safeguard and secure personal information about you.
COOKIES
A cookie is a small file, which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow webs applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We may set and use cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about our web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but can usually modify your browser settings to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES
Our website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information, which you provide while visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
YOUR INFORMATION
You can edit your MarineEngineParts.com account information at any time. You can request to stop receiving email updates and/or delete your account at any time. To make your request, please contact our customer service representatives at sales@partman.com
POLICY UPDATES
MarineEngineParts.com may update this policy at any time. We encourage you to review our Privacy Policy periodically.
